export const reactQnA = [
    {
        questionText: "Q.1. What's React and What are its advantages of it?",
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/react-js-qa#heading-q1-whats-react-and-what-are-its-advantages-of-it'
    },
    {
        questionText: "Q.2. What's Virtual DOM in React & What are its advantages of it?",
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/react-js-qa#heading-q2-whats-virtual-dom-in-react-andamp-what-are-its-advantages-of-ithttps://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/react-js-qa#heading-q2-whats-virtual-dom-in-react-andamp-what-are-its-advantages-of-it'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.3. Explain the Life Cycle of React Components.',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/react-js-qa#heading-q3-explain-the-life-cycle-of-react-components'
    },{
        questionText: "Q.4. What's the difference between Functional Components and Class Components?",
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/react-js-qa#heading-q4-whats-the-difference-between-functional-components-and-class-components'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.5. What are the hooks in React & Can we use Hooks in Class Components?',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/react-js-qa#heading-q5-what-are-the-hooks-in-react-andamp-can-we-use-hooks-in-class-components'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.6. What are the Life Cycle methods and their advantages of it?',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/react-js-qa#heading-q6-what-are-the-life-cycle-methods-and-their-advantages-of-it'
    },{
        questionText: "Q.7. What's useState Hook & Advantages of it?",
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/react-js-qa#heading-q7-whats-usestate-hook-andamp-advantages-of-it'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.8. Explain useEffect & Advantages of it.',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/react-js-qa#heading-q8-explain-useeffect-andamp-advantages-of-it'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.9. Explain Context API and Create a Minor Project on it',
        subQuestions: ['Create a dashboard and with the button clicking on that change theme to dark and light.'],
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/react-js-qa#heading-q9-explain-context-api-and-create-a-minor-project-on-it'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.10. Explain useReducer and its advantages.',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/react-js-qa#heading-q10-explain-usereducer-and-its-advantages'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.11. Build a TODO Web App using React and useReducer Hook.',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/react-js-qa#heading-q11-build-a-todo-web-app-using-react-and-usereducer-hook'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.12. Build a simple Counter App using React.',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/react-js-qa#heading-q12-build-a-simple-counter-app-using-react'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.13. Build Calculator App using React Only.',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/react-js-qa#heading-q13-build-calculator-app-using-react-only'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.14. Build a Tic Tac Toe Game using the Class Component of React.',
        linkToAnswer: '/reactjs/ticTacToe'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.15. Explain Prop Drilling & How can we avoid it?',
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/react-js-qa#heading-q15-explain-prop-drilling-andamp-how-can-we-avoid-it'
    },{
        questionText: 'Q.16. Create a Task Manager where the user can create tasks and see his task.',
        subQuestions: ['Redirect him to the task dashboard section after login', 'Use https://reqres.in/ API to authenticate the user and redirect him to the task manager dashboard where he can see his task and create it.'],
        linkToAnswer: 'https://sandeepkdasari.hashnode.dev/react-js-qa#heading-q16-create-a-task-manager-where-the-user-can-create-tasks-and-see-his-task'
    },
]